Contact

nicutammy@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tammyjohnson-msni-bsn-rn-82124011 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
NICU
NICU/PICU/PEDS
PALS

Tammy Johnson MSNI, BSN,RN

Clinical System Analyst at Alaska Native Tribal Health Consortium (ANTHC)

Anchorage, Alaska

Summary

I have been a NICU RN for 27 years. I added PICU and Pediatrics to my specialties in 2001. I started Travel Nursing in 2000 as I decided I needed to expand my knowledge base of Nursing practices from other units and hospitals. I have traveled to 42 countries and worked in Australia. I completed my Master's of Nursing Informatics in 2018 and currently work as a Nurse Analyst for Alaska Native Medical Center in the Informatics department.

Experience

Alaska Native Tribal Health Consortium (ANTHC) Clinical System Analyst October 2017 - Present (2 years 9 months) Anchorage, Alaska Area

Registered Nurse MSN, BSN, RN August 1992 - Present (27 years 11 months)

Travel RN
Travel RN
January 2000 - Present (20 years 6 months)

Education

South University

Masters of Nursing , Nursing Informatics · (2014 - 2017)

South University Online Masters Program
Bachelor's degree, Nursing Science (2014 - 2016)

Ga. Baptist School Of Nursing

RN, Nursing · (1988 - 1992)